<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<d:hotels xmlns:d="http://www.uts.edu.au/31284/team2/wsd"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.uts.edu.au/31284/team2/wsd hotels.xsd ">

	<d:hotel id="1">
		<d:name>Placeholder Hotel</d:name>
		<d:country>Australia</d:country>
		<d:state>New South Wales</d:state>
		<d:city>Sydney</d:city>
		<d:address>24-42 Fiction Ln.</d:address>
		<d:telephone>+61 (02) 9909 2441</d:telephone>
		<d:email>contact@placehotel.com.au</d:email>
		<d:image-url>TheShiodome.jpg</d:image-url>
		<d:description>Placeholder Hotel is a luxury five-star hotel located in the heart of Sydney’s central business district. This luxury hotel is surrounded by Sydney’s most exclusive shopping centres, such as the beautiful Queen Victoria Building and iconic Westfield Sydney and is within walking distance to all of Sydney’s famous landmarks and cultural attractions including the Sydney Harbour Bridge, Sydney Opera House and the beautiful Botanic Gardens.</d:description>
	</d:hotel>

	<d:hotel id="2">
		<d:name>Brilliant Inn</d:name>
		<d:country>USA</d:country>
		<d:state>New York</d:state>
		<d:city>New York City</d:city>
		<d:address>28 3rd Ave.</d:address>
		<d:telephone>+01 (01) 5823 4253</d:telephone>
		<d:email>contact@brillinn.com</d:email>
		<d:image-url>brillInn.jpg</d:image-url>
		<d:description>Experience the ultimate in comfort and convenience at Brilliant Inn. This brilliant, 30-story midtown Manhattan hotel evokes a contemporary statement in limestone and glass, just a stone's throw from Fifth Avenue. Enjoy the modern amenities at this fine midtown New York hotel, set within easy reach of Manhattan's most celebrated attractions. Sights near our 4-diamond midtown Manhattan hotel include Times Square, Broadway theaters, world-famous restaurants, art museums and corporate headquarters</d:description>
	</d:hotel>

	<d:hotel id="3">
		<d:name>Cozy Capsule Hotel</d:name>
		<d:country>Japan</d:country>
		<d:state>Tokyo Prefecture</d:state>
		<d:city>Tokyo</d:city>
		<d:address>5-3 Yaesu 1 Chome</d:address>
		<d:telephone>+41 (21) 5336 8766</d:telephone>
		<d:email>contact@capsule.co.jp</d:email>
		<d:image-url>ShinjukuKabukichoTower.jpg</d:image-url>
		<d:description>Cozy Capsule Hotel, a 5-star hotel ranking among the finest of Tokyo's luxury hotels, is conveniently located in the heart of the city. The hotel is perfectly placed for both business and leisure travelers. It is close to Tokyo's main business districts and the excitement of the Kasumigaseki, Roppongi, Ginza, and Akasaka areas. From Hotel Okura you can get to a subway station within five minutes on foot and to Tokyo's Narita Airport within a 70-minute drive.</d:description>
	</d:hotel>

	<d:hotel id="4">
		<d:name>The Gregory</d:name>
		<d:country>USA</d:country>
		<d:state>New York</d:state>
		<d:city>New York City</d:city>
		<d:address>42 W 35th St.</d:address>
		<d:telephone>+01 (21) 2947 0200</d:telephone>
		<d:email>info@thegregoryhotelnewyork.com</d:email>
		<d:image-url>thegregoryhotel.jpg</d:image-url>
		<d:description>The St. Gregory is located at 2033 M Street NW in downtown Washington, D.C. The hotel has 155 total guest rooms. Of these, 15 are one-bedroom suites and another 85 are one-bedroom suites with kitchens. Another 16 one-bedroom "sky suites" occupy the hotel's top floor. These have balconies, and provide good views of downtown and nearby monuments. The remaining 39 rooms are "deluxe" hotel rooms.</d:description>
	</d:hotel>

	<d:hotel id="5">
		<d:name>Iclub Sheung Wan Hotel</d:name>
		<d:country>China</d:country>
		<d:state>Hong Kong</d:state>
		<d:city>Hong Kong</d:city>
		<d:address>138 Bonham Strand St.</d:address>
		<d:telephone>+08 (52) 3963 6288</d:telephone>
		<d:email>contact@iclub-hotels.com</d:email>
		<d:image-url>Iclub.jpg</d:image-url>
		<d:description>iclub Sheung Wan Hotel is in Hong Kong. Free Wi-Fi access is available.Each room here includes cable TV and air conditioning. There is also an electric kettle. Featuring a shower, the private bathrooms also have a hairdryer and free toiletries. You can enjoy city views from the room. Extras include a safe. At iclub Sheung Wan Hotel there is a 24-hour front desk. Other facilities available at the property include a vending machine.</d:description>
	</d:hotel>

</d:hotels>
